https://a-la-carte-france-tours.com/privacy.html

TOURS
Burgundy (10 days)
Alsace (12)
Loire Valley (14)
Provence - Riviera (14)
Paris (3)
Jura, Alps (14)
South West (12)
Best of France (17)
Privacy Policy, Disclaimer, Terms & Conditions
Conditions and terms of use
A La Carte France Tours is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to any of the A La Carte France Tours web sites. While visiting A La Carte France Tours web sites (collectively, the "Site"), we may ask you to register and/or provide information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") for purposes of interacting with the Site. To further the protection of your Personal Information, A La Carte France Tours has adopted a set of information management guidelines (outlined below) which serve as the basis for our customer relationship. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page.
Information collected
At this stage, cookies are not used by A La Carte France Tours. A La Carte France Tours allows selected advertisers to display interesting offers on its site, and these ads may contain cookies. We do not collect any personally identifiable information about our website's visitors. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Use of Personal Information
A La Carte France Tours does not share user information with third parties. A La Carte France Tours will use reasonable efforts to ensure that only our employees or consultants with a need to know will have access to your information. We do not release personal information about you as an individual to third parties.
Credit card details
A La Carte France Tours encourages you to use a secure payment medium for forwarding your credit card details, as described during your booking correspondence. Please follow the steps suggested to ensure that your credit card details remain confidential. Once received by A La Carte France Tours, your credit card details will be handled only by approved employees or consultants within A La Carte France Tours, and forwarded in a secure manner to A La Carte France Tours' bank for processing. A La Carte France Tours will not use your credit card details for any other purpose than payment processing and will not forward it to any exterior person or organization. Your credit card will be charged only for the amounts explicitly agreed upon and its details will not be held as security.
Links to Other Materials
If any link is offered connecting you to a third party web site, it is as an accommodation to the respective third party site owner and without charge. Third party sites linked to and from the Site are not necessarily under the control of A La Carte France Tours. A La Carte France Tours shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. A La Carte France Tours does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the Site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the Site, you do so entirely at your own risk. A La Carte France Tours hereby disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, copyrights, patents, domain names or other intellectual property interests of third parties.
Children's Privacy
A La Carte France Tours cares about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.
Airline Responsibility and Liability
The sole and exclusive responsibility and liability of any IATA carrier used , shall be in accordance with and as limited by the contract of carriage in the passenger's ticket when issued, the applicable tariffs, and the provisions of the Warsaw Convention, if applicable. Any carrier used shall not be responsible or liable for any act, omission, or occurrence during the time passengers are not on board its airplanes. All tours, services, and transportation (other than air) are furnished by contractors that are independent and that do not act for or on behalf of the carrier, nor are servants of the same, and neither do they have any business relationship, as joint ventures or otherwise.
Further, the carrier shall not be responsible or liable in any way for the accuracy of any representations of the tour operator and its agents on tours or tour services other than those contained in the tour brochures or tour itineraries. Carrier liability for passenger's baggage is clearly stated on the passenger contract included on all tickets or can be found on file for inspection at the offices of the carrier. Liability for checked and unchecked baggage shall in no event exceed the actual loss incurred by the passenger, subject to proof of the amount of the loss.
Overbooking of Flights
Airline flights may be overbooked, and there is a slight chance that a seat will not be available on a flight for which a person has a confirmed reservation. If the flight is overbooked, no one will be denied a seat until airline personnel first ask for volunteers willing to give up their reservation in exchange for a payment of the airline's choosing. If there are not enough volunteers the airline will deny boarding to other persons in accordance with its particular boarding priority. With few exceptions persons denied boarding involuntarily are entitled to compensation.
The complete rules for the payment of compensation and each airline's boarding priorities are available at all airport ticket counters and boarding locations.
Some airlines do not apply these consumer protections to travel from some foreign countries, although other consumer protections may be available. Check with the airline.
Disclaimer
RESPONSIBILITY: A La Carte France Tours and/or agents and officers and/or suppliers of services pursuant to, or in connection with these itineraries, shall act only as agents for the passenger in making arrangements for hotels, transportation, restaurants or any other service and does not assume any liability whatsoever for any injury, damage, death, loss, accidents, incidents or delay to any person or property due to an act of negligence of or default of any hotel, carrier, restaurant, company or person rendering any of the services included in the tour or by an act of God. Further, no responsibilities are accepted for any damage or delay due to sickness, pilferage, labor disputes, machinery breakdown, quarantine, government restraints, weather or other causes beyond their personal control. No responsibility is accepted for any additional expense, omissions, delays, re-routing or acts of any government or authority. The airlines concerned are not to be held responsible for any act, omission or event during the time passengers are not on board their planes or conveyances. The passage contract in use by the airlines concerned, when issued, shall constitute the sole contract between the airlines and purchaser of these tours and/or passenger . The right is reserved to withdraw any program in this offer and/or make such changes in the program(s) as may be found desirable for the convenience of the parties and the proper carrying out of tour(s).
THE PRICES OF THESE VACATION PACKAGES, AND/OR AIRLINE TICKETS AND/OR CRUISE PACKAGES ARE BASED ON RATES IN EFFECT AT THE TIME OF PUBLISHING AND ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE.
A La Carte France Tours do not assume any responsibility for errors or omissions on this web site. Please note that the persons, vehicles, establishments, places, attractions and other features depicted or described on this website may not be part of your actual tour depending on availability and circumstances.
Itinerary Changes
Due to the nature of expeditions, tour packages, excursions and/or other services provided; weather, acts of God, government, and/or airline regulations may require changes to be made to the itineraries and/or the cancellation of certain excursions or add-ons. Every attempt will be made to adhere to the itineraries described within the limits of safety and time. In the event of changes, passengers have no right to any refund or other compensation, for these tours, excursions, accommodations and/or transportations, except where provided by the particular providers of said services. Expedition, excursions, and/or tour fees are based on group participation.
Should you choose not to take part in any activity or make use of services provided, no refund will be made.
Passport and Visas
It is the passenger(s) responsibility to obtain any and all documents required for travel, including, but not limited to valid passports, exit and/or entry/re-entry visas, and any other documents required by the respective immigration officials of the country/ies you are to visit and/or return to, as well as any required and/or needed vaccinations prior or after your travel.
Booking, Payments, Cancellations and Refunds
Booking, Payments, Cancellations and Refunds policies as specified on your individual offer apply to your individual booking. Standard policy applied by A La Carte France Tours is:
30% non-refundable deposit to secure your booking (usually ca 6 months before the tour)
70% to be paid 60 days before the beginning of the tour
Cancellations: the 30% deposit is non refundable; 20% of balance refunded for cancellations received in writing until the day before departure; no refund for cancellations received later.
Inclusions
Please refer to your individual offer for an exact description of what is included in the price of your tour. Usually, and on all tours listed on this website, this price includes:
Boutique/ luxury: private driver-guide or driver-chauffeur, transport, private local guides, all entrance fees as per suggested itinerary, accommodation in boutique style or luxury small hotels and Bed & Breakfasts (comfortable double room with private bathroom), continental breakfasts, light lunches (i.e. quiche, sandwich, soup), dinners in fine cuisine restaurants (3 items to choose freely à la carte) with locally produced wine (half bottle per dinner per person), all soft drinks, all taxes and tolls. This price does not include: personal expenses, insurance, international flights, drinks other than mentioned and optional activities.
See examples of hotels and restaurants corresponding to each of these categories.
Effective Date and Changes
This Privacy Policy is effective as of 17 November 2016. A La Carte France Tours reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of the Site following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.
Tour Selection
Burgundy
Dijon, Beaune, Macon, Bourg en Bresse
Days 10
Alsace
Alsace, Lorraine, Strasbourg
12
Loire Valley
Information
Please feel free to enquire about any custom-made tours in France. We are always happy to suggest an itinerary for your specific needs. We regret however we are unable to accept bookings for tours shorter than 10 days.
Privacy Policy, Disclaimer
Terms & Conditions
A LA CARTE FRANCE TOURS
toll-free USA-Canada: +1-888-588-8923
Phone USA:
Burgundy (10 days)
Alsace (12)
Loire Valley (14)
Provence - Riviera (14)
Paris (3)
Jura, Alps (14)
South West (12)
Best of France (17)
